

# Sherkhan **Tulkibay**



# **DESIRED POSITION**

# Frontent developer

#### **ABOUT**

Front-end developer with experience:

- creating a SPA using React JS and Redux;
- creating static websites using Gatsby JS and Strapi.

I have knowledge in the field of user interface, testing and debugging. Now I am improving my skills in this direction and expanding them with the help of new technologies.

Capable of effective self-management, as well as team collaboration.

Open for your suggestions



### **EDUCATION**

**ENU** (Master's degree)

2016-2018

"Space technique and technology"

KazATU (Bachelor's degree)

2010-2014

"Radiotechnic, electronic and telecommunications"



### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **State Technical Service JSC**

# Front-end developer

06.2021-Present

- layout interfaces according to the layout, write new functionality, maintain and develop the design system. Project stack (Laravel, PostgreSQL, JS, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap)

#### Department of information and commincation MIA RK 07.2015-06.2021 Senior engineer

- technical support of video conferencing
- technical support for local network and telephony
- development of technical specifications
- perform official duties in a timely and high-quality manner documents

# **Technical support center of ENU Engineer**

11.2014-07.2015

- technical support for local network and telephony
- current repair of computer equipment
- installation and maintenance of university buildings software solutions

# **PORTFOLIO**

Attps://sherkhan61.github.io/portfolio-2/



## CONTACTS



+7 777 774 1361



🕅 sherkhan-92@bk.ru



Nur-Sultan, Kazakhstan



linkedin.com/in/sherkhan-tulkibay



https://github.com/sherkhan61



t.me/sherkhan61



# **ADDITIONALLY**

# My motto

Follow your DREAMS and the Universe will open doors FOR YOU where there were ONLY WALLS



## **LANGUAGES**

English: A2



# **SKILLS**

- + JavaScript
- + TypeScript
- + React JS
- + Gatsby JS
- + Strapi
- + HTML5
- + CSS3
- + SCSS
- + Flexbox

- + Redux
- + Axios
- + GraphQL
- + Bootstrap
- + Material UI
- + Formik
- + Git